meltingpot.com 2019-03-05

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

The following information explains our policy regarding any personal information you may supply to us when visiting our site. The Melting Pot's goal in collecting personal information online is to provide you with a personalized web experience. By knowing your preferences we can deliver relevant information that meets your needs, and ensures that your visit to our site is quick, easy, and productive.

The Melting Pot collects personally identifying information only (1) when you register for personalized information at our site, (2) to place an order in our shopping cart, and (3) to enter into one of our promotions. The Melting Pot will not sell, rent, or share this information with any other organization.

### Cookies

Our web-site will request that we put a cookie on your computer. Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. The information stored will make your usage of our site easier and faster because it allows you to use the site without having to re-enter information on each visit. The cookies also keep track of your configured products and the items stored in your shopping list, so you can search our site for more information or configure another product without losing the configured product information that you created.

We also use cookies when you request personalized information on our site. These cookies are used to identify visitors when they return to the site. They also maintain the visitor's identity while at our site so they need only log in once. Without cookies, the shopping cart (which maintains your items from page to page) will not function.

The Melting Pot does not use cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in the cookie, and we do not use information transferred through cookies for any promotional or marketing purposes, nor is that information shared with any third parties whatsoever.

### Security

We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. You can confirm this by noting the small yellow lock which appears on the bottom of your browser window during the checkout process.

We reveal only five digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.

Credit card information is stored in our database using triple-DES encryption algorithms, to guarantee that, even if someone were able to gain access to the data, nothing useful could be extracted.

By using this site, you signify your agreement with The Melting Pot Privacy Policy. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time. Your continued use of our site following changes to these terms means you accept those changes.
